=Episode 5=
♪I shut out the world, you're all I see♪
♪One glance to last forever,
just you and me♪
Xi Yuan,
don't let your inner demon consume you.
Jin Yunlie.
Come with me.
♪Hard to forget the losses of the past♪
Help me.
♪The wind hasn't risen tonight.
Missing you might be an illness♪
♪The long misty rain scatters in haste♪
♪Letting go may be love's last line♪
You're not left with nothing.
The past
is behind you now.
What's in your world right now
is the present and the future.
Right.
I'm not left with nothing.
♪Who can forget the dreams
once held and lost♪
♪Petals on your shoulder reveal your charm♪
Xia Honglian,
my past may be full of darkness,
but you can't destroy me
with those memories.
♪After the world fades away,
you alone stay in my sight♪
What's past
is prologue.
Break!
Jin Yunlie,
so it was you just now.
Honglian!
Father!
How dare you!
How dare you touch my father!
Let him go right now!
The Xia family's crimes are ironclad.
You're
coming with us too.
What?
Heavens!
You've treated my family unfairly!
Unfairly!
Father!
Jin Yunlie,
today,
you have brought ruin
upon my family.
I will paint this arena red with blood!
What are you doing?
Great Lord Qing Yuluo above,
I offer my blood
to summon your presence!
Qing Yuluo?
Oh my!
The Second Prince of Longyuan Kingdom?
Yes.
What's he doing here?
Yeah, what for?
Qing Yuluo,
you colluded with the Xia family
and stirred up all this chaos,
yet your brother Qing Zeyuan
dares not show up?
Oh?
You mean that stubborn,
good-for-nothing royal brother?
After Longyuan's guardian deity died,
Longyuan was left without a protector,
desperate for shelter.
And he, with his rigid mind,
refused to pledge allegiance
to the Great Demon Lord.
So I had no choice but to replace him.
The Demon Lord is the most
malevolent force in this world.
The four kingdoms sealed him away
and made a pact a century ago.
Now you have broken that pact,
murdered your brother
to seize the throne,
turned to the Demon Lord,
and colluded with the Xia family.
What is your goal?
You want to know that?
Fight me one on one,
and I'll tell you.
Outrageous!
How dare you wreak havoc
in the Huyun Imperial Palace
and provoke His Highness!
Seize him!
Yes, seize him!
A bunch of nonentities,
and you think you can stop me?
(Qing Yuluo.)
Great Demon Lord?
(Wipe this place clean for me.)
Understood.
Demon Spirit!
Demon Spirits have descended!
Help!
Help us!
Jin Yunlie.
If you want to stop all this,
then face me and prove your worth.
So arrogant.
Jin Yunlie, beat him up!
Send him back where he came from!
You talk too much.
Lou Jingou,
get her out of here.
Right away.
Hey! You...
Go, now!
In that case,
let's have a little sparring match.
No rules, to the death.
Jin Yunlie,
Huyun has kept Xuanji Jade
for far too long.
Now,
it's time for a change.
You're delusional.
Am I?
Qing Yuluo,
I told you,
you don't have what it takes
to fight me.
So cool!
Crawl back to your own territory!
This demon blade devours souls
without a trace.
Farewell, Jin Yunlie.
I missed.
Xi Yuan!
Why did you...
Didn't I tell you?
You saved me,
and I'd save you.
We're even now.
This woman...
Xi Yuan!
No way.
Now I have to forge a new puppet.
Great Demon Lord.
Useless waste.
You wasted a drop of my blood,
and you still couldn't kill that man.
My Lord, please stay your anger.
Killing Jin Yunlie failed this time,
but I gained something valuable.
The princess of the Huangyan Clan,
who fled into exile years ago,
has shown up in Huyun.
We can use this woman
to sow discord between Huyun
and Huangyan.
We can also use her
as leverage against Jin Yunlie.
Huangyan?
(How ridiculous.)
(In this world, no one
even knows your true identity.)
(After all these years,)
(we finally meet again.)
No need to sow discord.
All you need to do is capture that woman
and bring her here.
♪My regret came too late,
I finally see your true face♪
♪My shattered promises struggle,
how can I let go♪
♪Stripped bare, tormented.
I flinch at every feeling♪
♪Forced to yield,
I flee before I fall apart♪
♪I hate your back,
endless, blank, and never clear♪
♪Watching me weep, yet you stay silent♪
♪I hate how you cast me aside,
yet no room for a word♪
♪I hate my silence, my fading self,
and my lack of spite♪
♪Yet I still hope you'll save me♪
♪By the end,
I'm just your leftover compromise♪
♪All the excuses I made for you♪
♪Proud yet humble, I loved you♪
♪Just like before, nothing has changed♪
♪I had no escape from
that heart-wrenching agony♪
♪Love became my sin,
we once were whole and wild♪
Xi Yuan,
I won't let you die.
♪I hate your back,
endless, blank, and never clear♪
♪Watching me weep, yet you stay silent♪
♪I hate how you cast me aside,
yet no room for a word♪
♪A love letter, a passionate pursuit,
the envy of everyone♪
♪Bouquets and heartfelt confessions,
leaving me moved and fulfilled♪
♪No matter how long or hard our road,
I don't care♪
♪But you left me with this pain,
forever beyond redemption♪